

## **PROFILE**

Efficient and Enthusiastic professional with 3+ years of industrial experience as a full stack developer in .NET stack along with angular framework.

Worked on Significant project features using asp.net MVC architecture which automates the financial statements preparation

Responsible for building block of code in C#, Designing views with html, CSS, And Validating the user inputs and their activity with JS, jQuery.

Also responsible for developing single page component in angular8.

Also familiar with agile scrum methodology.

I thrive to work in a challenging environment and ready to transform the unexpected obstacles into steppingstones for achievements."

#### CONTACT

PHONE:

+91 - 9542911419

+91 - 8074597873

EMAIL:

rajuatuoh@gmail.com

#### **HOBBIES**

Running Working Out Audio Books

# RAJU KUMAR SAHU

+3 years of Industrial experience as Full Stack Developer. ASP.NET MVC, Angular, jQuery, TypeScript, Html, CSS, SQL Server, IIS, Data-Structure.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **University of Hyderabad**

2014 - 17

Secured 61.9% in **MCA** with Programming Methodology, Algorithms, DBMS, Computer Networks, OOPs, Systems Security, Accounting and Financial Management, Computer Based Numerical and Statistical Methods and lot more

#### Ranchi College, Ranchi

2010 - 14

Secured 61.9% In BSC-Computer Application.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Ernst & Young, Technical Associate, FAAS (Nov-2018 – Till Date)

FRH - Financial Reporting Hub. nov2019 - nov2020.

Contributed as front-end developer by developing angular components along with data validation, business logic, API integration for project, which automates the financial statements preparation

> CFR- Comprehensive Financial Reporting Tool nov2018-nov2019 Developed the MVC-based user interface as front end and business logic along with the implementation of third-party API's.

Deploy the project on the client's environment and apricated for resolving the severe bugs in real time.

#### Genpact, Technical trainee (Jul-2017 – nov-2018)

Micro Home Finance, apr2018- oct2018.

Actively contributed in design of object-oriented architecture for a MSME business that provides the Multilevel role-based user groups for various jobs for home finance process of customer. Which helps to KYC of customer and their authentication management and process the loan.

> Two-Wheeler vehicle Finance, aug2017- mar2018.

Actively contributed in end to end process from UI design to business logic along with data handling for the module of user verification, status analysis.

#### **SKILLS**

